

Polkovnikov Nikita

Product Designer / Manager

Citezenship: Bulgaria

E-mail: **nekiteth@gmail.com**

Telegram: **nekiteth**

Behance: **behance.net/nekiteth**

About

I have been designing for over 6 years - I started with graphic design and then transitioned to UI/UX and Product Design. For the last 4 years, I have worked as a Product Designer with management responsibilities in various product teams.

Now I am looking for a remote **Product Designer / Manager** position in a startup (round A or higher) or a product company with a startup approach.

Experience

KrewGuru - HR tech platform for maritime personnel

Product Designer / Design Lead Full-time

Dec 2020 - Present · 1 yr 8 mos

In Krew Guru, I was solely responsible for creating all design layouts and prototypes and worked on the MVP with the CEO and Project Manager.

When preparing features, I always considered product aspects and technical metrics to optimize product performance.

- · Created an MVP using hypotheses validated via CustDev;
- · Built from scratch a unique design system;
- · Optimized designs using analytical data from Amplitude and GA;
- · Formulated tasks for analysts and designer, prepared product descriptions for developers;
- Developed and implemented a solution that allowed seafarers to reduce the time it takes to create a CV by 3 times (compared to major competitors);
- Conducted qualitative and quantitative research (needs and behavioral patterns of B2B and B2C users), etc.

MyAtom - Physics learning center for children

Product Designer / Manager | Contract

Jul 2020 - Dec 2020 · 6 mos

- · Created features based on hypotheses generated and tested during CustDev;
- · Created a product for maintaining statistics at learning centers;
- · Worked with a new for me target group children 12-16 years old;
- Lined up the entire process of implementing new features in a timeframe from initiation to release:
- · Assigned tasks to developers and designers;
- Personally went through the entire process of uploading the finished app to the AppStore and Google Play.

Polygled - Language exchange platform for native speakers

Product Designer Full time

Sep 2019 - Jun 2020 · 10 mos

- · Conducted research to improve metrics and close user pains;
- · Improved user return metrics method to improve usability;
- · Attracted more than 50,000 active users (DAU);
- Personally went through the entire process of uploading the finished app to the AppStore and Google Play.

KICK - Cryptocurrency exchange

Product Designer | Contract

May 2019 - Sep 2019 · 5 mos

- · Researched all the intricacies of crypto exchanges to improve UX;
- · Performed detailed research and CustDev to create new features;
- · Prototyped new interfaces for all needs;
- · Performed UX usability tests.

PLOY - Outsourcing agency

Product Designer / Manager Full time

November 2018 - May 2019 · 7 mos

- · Conducted market analysis for clients' projects;
- · Created Sketch prototypes and handed them into development;
- · Reviewed developers/designers' work.

Education	Skills & Tools
Bachelor of Journalism	Qualitative and quantitative
RSUH - In progress	research, JTBD, Analytics, Mirro,
Specialist in computer networks	Figma, Jira, Notion, GA, Amplitude
MGKIT - Completed 2018	
Languages:	Hobbies:
English (Upper-Intermediate)	Basketball, Crypto, WEB3, Music,
Russian (Native)	Sneakers, Travels